Next, we need to unzip the file,
接下来 我们需要解压文件
then open the extracted files so that we can see and work with the data inside.
然后打开解压文件 从而看到并使用文件中的数据
We'll do both programmatically and therefore reproducibly,
我们需要采取编程方式和可再现方式
and we'll do both in our Jupyter Notebook.
可通过 Jupyter Notebook 完成
So first things first,
先说重要的
we need to open up a Jupyter Notebook.
我们需要打开 Jupyter Notebook
We can do that by typing Jupyter Notebook in
我们可以在 Mac 或 Linux 系统的终端上输入 Jupyter Notebook
our terminal on Mac or Linux or command prompt on PC.
或在 PC 机上输入命令提示符
Before we do that though,
在我们操作之前
a notebook server will start in whatever directory we run this command in,
应在运行命令的目录下开启 Notebook 服务器
which means any notebook files will be saved in that directory.
这意味着 Notebook 文件将保存在那个目录之下
And external files like our downloaded data set,
在目录之下
are most easily imported when in this directory.
我们更容易导入外部文件 比如下载的数据集
So I'm going to navigate to the folder I want to work in which is called
我将导航到将要使用的文件夹位置 “data wrangling”
data wrangling which is within a folder in my documents called Udacity.
它位于我的文档中 “Udacity” 文件夹中
So from my home directory,
从我的主目录
all changed directories or cd to documents,
改变目录 或者输入 cd Documents
then cd to Udacity and finally change directories to data wrangling.
然后 cd udacity 最后 cd data-wrangling
And now we can enter our Jupyter Notebook command.
现在我们可以输入 Jupyter Notebook 命令
Okay. So here we can see our Jupyter Notebook dashboard
好的 我们看到 Jupyter Notebook 面板
which shows a list of the notebooks,
上面显示 Notebook、文件和子目录清单
files and sub-directories in the directory where the notebook server was started.
它们都在启动 Notebook 服务器的目录下
Here we can create new notebooks by clicking New in Python
我们可以创建新的 Notebook
3 or you can use
只需点击 Python 3 中的 New (新建) 或者你可以使用
the wrangling template notebook that's available for download which I put in this folder,
整理模板 Notebook 我放在了这个文件夹下
which you can see here.
可供你下载
Side note: IPYNB stands for I Python Notebook,
旁注: IPYNB 表示 I Python Notebook
which is the old name for Jupyter Notebooks.
这是 Jupyter Notebook 的旧名
And I'll click that. And there we go.
点击它 会出现这个页面
We've opened up a Jupyter Notebook.
我们打开了一个 Jupyter Notebook